# Leigh Warner

CONTACT 128 Donomore Ave

Killinarden

Dublin

E-mail: leighwarner3@gmail.com

Website: <a href="https://github.com/LeighWarner99">https://github.com/LeighWarner99</a>,

www.linkedin.com/in/leigh-warner-

**Phone:** 0858486800

**PROFILE** 

Recent graduate from Technological University Dublin where I obtained my degree in Computing with Data Analytics. Acquired my knowledge and experience from working on projects while attending college and my internship. Vast knowledge of programming languages and cloud technologies. I am extremely excited to join a workplace and bring my skills and knowledge to the company and further my expertise in the field.

**EDUCATION** 

Bachelors Honours Degree in Computing with Data Analytics

Technological University Dublin

Final GPA - 3.0 Second Class Honors grade 1

**Modules Studied:** Applied Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning (C+), Enterprise Performance Architecture (B+), IT Governance and Quality (B-), Project (B), Interactive Media Design (B+), Information Management (C+), Social Media Analysis (A), Data Analysis and Programming (C+), Applied Machine Learning (B-).

Software Development

September 2016 — May 2017

September 2017 — May 2021

Greenhill's College

**Modules Studied:** Web Authoring, Networking, Games Design, Software Architecture. Math's, Fundamentals of Object Oriented Programming, Mobile Technologies, Work Experience, Communications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Electrical Supply Board**

January 2020 — August 2020

**Enterprise Services** 

- Provide constant feedback/support to the manager.
- Work closely with team members on day-to-day tasks.
- Automating day-to-day tasks using PowerShell scripts.
- Point of contact for the creation of new user accounts via MDMS database.
- Obtaining information through SQL scripts about new Smart meters, analyzing information, and making sure new meters were AMR ready.
- Work closely with security team when running PowerShell scripts through virtual machines to gather and collect information on patch updates for Smart meters.

### The Galway Hooker

November 2018 — August 2020

Bar Man

- Provide feedback to the manager about sales.
- Dealing with complex problems customers may have.
- Interpersonal skills to sell/upsell products.
- Stock replenishing when required.
- Maintaining a clean working environment.
- Working closely with members of the bar team to make sure customer satisfaction was good.
- Manage refunds/problems for customers.
- Accessing customers' needs/preferences and making recommendations.

Leigh Warner

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Final year project overview:

Emotion detection through image classification. Data selection and preparation of images to expand dataset for project. Training data using Python's built-in libraries such as **Tensor Flow, Pandas, NumPy**, and **Sklearn.** Development and fine tuning of Convolutional Neural Network to gain the best models for predictions on unseen data. Use of pre-existing CNN models like **VGG-16**, **RESNET-50**, and **Inception-V3**. Predictions made on unseen images to allow models to accurately make predictions. Compared results and made conclusions on the best models.

#### e-Commerce Website overview:

This project consisted of a three-man team in which an e-commerce website was designed using **UML**, **play framework**, **Scala**, **JavaScript**, **eBeans DB**, **Bootstrap**, and **jQuery**. During the creation of the e-commerce site, bootstrap was used throughout for design and added functionality throughout the site. There was a **CRUD** system in place which allowed for different level of users to access the site, users such as administrator, manager, and a regular user. We implemented **Stripe** for our cart functionality, which allowed for fake transactions to occur to simulate real-time transactions taking place. The project was conducted within an Agile environment which included reporting to our supervisor each week on further developments in the project.

#### IT SKILLS

- Coding Languages Java, C++, Python, C#, JavaScript, PowerShell
- Designing websites using HTML, CSS, Scala, Bootstrap, NoSQL, SQL
- Efficient user of Windows and Linux Operation Systems
- Understanding of Machine Learning & AI model based development
- Knowledge of AWS technologies
- Capable user of cloud computing concepts such as Databases, Networking, Routing Switching, IP/DNS

#### **INTERESTS**

- Sports
- Reversegameengineering
- Participatinginaband
- Volunteer Give my time to the local community on big clean ups of the area

#### REFERENCES

References available upon request.